Contact

Dublin - Ireland + 353 83 183 3805 (Mobile) cesargarcia.elder@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cesar-garcia-637973aa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HTML5

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
JavaScript

Certifications

JavaScript Course

Cesar Garcia

Housekeeper at The National Maternity Hospital County Dublin, Ireland

Summary

I'm a motivated, dedicated, and highly skilled professional in the healthcare environment. I have over 5 years of experience working in the hospitality industry. I bring many transferable skills, like customer service, communication, teamwork, inventory management, response to emergency calls, rules and regulations. Recently working in a hospital I learned how to deal with COVID-19 infections and how to maintain the facilities in full compliance with the hospital regulations.

Experience

The National Maternity Hospital Housekeeper March 2020 - Present (3 years 4 months) Dublin, Ireland

I'm working as a housekeeper as part of the Covid Team in infection control, minimizing and managing the risk of infections, sanitizing the healthcare environment in full compliance with the hospital regulations and safety, also respond to any emergency call having all the precautions and safety to meet their necessities at work.

TRYP by Wyndham Senior Receptionist | Manager Assistant February 2019 - February 2020 (1 year 1 month) São Paulo, Brazil

I worked as a Senior Bilingual Receptionist and Manager Assistant dealing not only with check-ins or check-outs of a big hotel group but also committed to improving our workflow and managing the team to get the best results and achieve our goals weekly in compliance with the audit department of the hotel.

Pullman Hotels & Resorts Night Auditor June 2017 - January 2019 (1 year 8 months) São Paulo, Brazil I started working as a Junior Bilingual Receptionist and quickly delivered enough performance to be promoted to junior night auditor after a few months had an opportunity to take over the main responsibilities and started working as a Senior Night Auditor, which gave me the opportunity of improving my skills and get know the whole picture of how a big hotel group reception works in the backstage.

Invoice

IT Support Technician

December 2009 - December 2011 (2 years 1 month)

São Paulo, Brazil

I worked in the company's technical support and the analysis of infrastructure, and automation

of processes in Shell Script. I worked with Windows users assisting with their needs, in the part of maintenance, network, and software administration.

Education

Code Institute

NFQ Level 6, Full Stack Developer Course · (January 2023 - December 2023)

Mimo Bootcamp

Certificate, Computer Software and Media Applications · (April 2023 - April 2023)

CodeCademy

Certificate, JavaScript · (January 2023 - February 2023)

Code Institute

5 Day Coding Challenge, HTML, CSS and JavaScript · (January 2023 - January 2023)

ICOT College

Certificate, English for Business · (October 2015 - June 2017)